{
    "id": "74e158af2ea94a449db5335f36f0bcc5",
    "title": "Much and Many Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. are called but few are chosen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have told you ……………. times that I do not like horror movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She does not have ……………. friends in town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The writer is ……………… revered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you go there ……………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ……………. money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got ……………. work ahead of us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of the hype, the film is not ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has acted in …………… Kannada movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………. of the roof needs repairing?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}